Guide to the Collective: Unconscious Archive 1995-2008 (bulk 1998-2004) MSS 225
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Administrative Files
  - Subseries C: Financial
    - Receipts, ledger, and other misc. financial records, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Checking account statements and other financial reports, 1998-2001 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Checks and check stubs, 1998-2002 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Checks, 1998-2002 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Operating reports and tax records, 1998-2002 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Fire protection receipts/reports, 1999-2001 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Checks and check stubs, 1999-2002 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Electric bills (ConEd), 1999-2002 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Garbage and city waste invoices, 1999-2002 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Receipts, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Petty cash receipts, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Misc. financial records, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Deposits, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Receipts, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Deposits, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Deposits, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Deposits, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Not-For-Profit/Tax exemption records, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Tax exemption records, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Fundraising/grant files, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Tax exempt info/forms (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Misc. receipts [IFAM?], undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Donations, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Series III: Photographic Material
  Series III: Photographic Material contains negatives, slides, and photographs pertaining to Collective members and activities. This series includes a large volume of snapshots, interspersed with what appear to be production shots and a few promotional images. Many of the photographs appear to be water-damaged and most lack documentation.
  - Slides - misc., 1994-2000 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    photographer: Allan B. Spiegel
  - Photographs - misc. "Monster Parade", [ca. 1996-2000] (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Photographs - "Shrimpdiabloinmypants Film Festival", [1999] (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Photographs - Charlie Victor Romeo, [ca. 1999-2001] (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Photographs - "Dinner Performance", 9/24/00, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Negatives and Photographs - "5th Annual Monster Parade", [2000] (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Negatives - misc., undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Photographs - misc., undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Photographs - misc., undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Photographs - misc., undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Photographs - misc., undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Photographs - head shots, undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Photocopies [postcard size] (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Photocopies, undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Series IV: Realia
  Series IV: Realia contains a variety of objects likely used as stage props as well as a small number of artworks.
  Box 8 will be stored with other oversize materials.
  - Tristan Perich, "One Bit Music" (Cantaloupe Music), 2004-2005 (Box 8, Object ID: 225.2.0001)
  - Artwork - Matthew Deleget, "Fortress", 2000 (Box 8, Object ID: 225.2.0002)
    Silver metallic ink on black handmade paper on masonite board
  - Artwork - C. Smith [untitled harbor scene], undated (Box 8, Object ID: 225.2.0003)
    matted photocopy
  - Artwork [untitled nudes collage], undated (Box 8, Object ID: 225.2.0004)
    pencil, paint, and pastel on canvas
  - Artwork - A.R. Ceheralu [sp?], "Nike Tsunami #17", 2005 (Box 8, Object ID: 225.2.0005)
    holographic tile
  - Artwork - [Hitler cutout], undated (Box 8, Object ID: 225.2.0006)
    marker and crayon on wax paper
  - Sketchbook - Gecko, undated (Box 8, Object ID: 225.2.0007)
  - Artwork - Jake Young [?], "Happy 10th Faceboy!", undated (Box 8, Object ID: 225.2.0008)
  - Woven fabric portrait [Karl Marx], undated (Box 8, Object ID: 225.2.0009)
  - "Borscht Belt" decorated wrestling belt, undated (Box 9, Object ID: 225.2.0010)
  - Promotional coffee cups [4], C:U and Coffee Cup Productions, 2001 (Box 9, Object ID: 225.2.0011)
  - "Arsenal" perfume cannister [in shape of grenade], undated (Box 9, Object ID: 225.2.0012)
  - Metal bike horn, undated (Box 9, Object ID: 225.2.0013)
  - Toy gun, undated (Box 9, Object ID: 225.2.0014)
  - Toy gun, undated (Box 9, Object ID: 225.2.0015)
  - Toy gun, undated (Box 9, Object ID: 225.2.0016)
  - Disposable camera, undated (Box 9, Object ID: 225.2.0017)
  - Antique telephone, 1945 (Box 9, Object ID: 225.2.0018)
  - Toy knife, undated (Box 9, Object ID: 225.2.0019)
  - Doorbell, undated (Box 9, Object ID: 225.2.0020)
  - Clear plastic tubing, undated (Box 9, Object ID: 225.2.0021)
  - Mirror ball christmas ornaments, undated (Box 9, Object ID: 225.2.0022)
  - Furry red glove, undated (Box 9, Object ID: 225.2.0023)
  - Transparent red scarf, undated (Box 9, Object ID: 225.2.0024)
  - Event lanyards - "Auto-Historical Anniversary Event 5", 4/8/2000 (Box 9, Object ID: 225.2.0025)
- Series V: Video
  Series V: Video includes original footage of Collective: Unconscious productions, commercial videos, as well as source material collected as background research for productions and as documentation of other avant-garde artists. Subseries B, Originals includes recordings on various media of Collective: Unconscious performances. The bulk of material documents the anti-slams, episodes of Manifestations, and Faceboy. Series C, Miscellaneous, contains recordings collected by Collective: Unconscious, including commercial films, independent productions by contemporary and avant-garde artists, mixed recordings of source materials (primarily archival footage and television productions), and unidentified tapes.
  Subseries A: Access Copies
  Subseries B: Originals
  Subseries C: Miscellaneous
  - Subseries A: Access Copies
    Conditions Governing Access
    Access copies for video originals may not yet be available. Please contact a Fales Archivist.
  - Subseries B: Originals
    - "New Year's"; "Video Theme Party", July 22, 1990 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0001)
      Currently unavailable until duplication occurs.
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
      Original format: VHS
    - "Gay Tards + Mini Red Satan, Surf Reality (1st NY perf.)", November 22, 2000 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0002)
    - "Carmen Mofongo, Fiesta de Amor", February 11, 2005 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0003)
    - "Feb 29, 2004; Matchgame '04", February 29, 2004 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0004)
    - "To Hug U + Squeeze You (Kreider); Black Lagoon, It's Alive (Marv); His Holy Prepose (Gang); Industrial Synth (S Price); SSsion, Anorexia... (Cody); Sex Machine, Death Becomes Her 9 Times (Biddle)", undated (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0016)
    - "Jacinto" (related to CVR?), undated (Box 10, Media ID: 225/0019)
    - "718-768-9079; AB25 OLOM, copy B1" [Subseries C?], January 16, 2000 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0023)
    - "Stuff + AntiSlam Part 1", June 30, 2004 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0036)
    - "Air Force Shoot", undated (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0039)
      Original format: MiniDV
    - "Air Force Shoot", undated (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0040)
    - "Ana Montana; CGC", March 2001; April 22, 2001 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0041)
      Original format: Video 8
    - "AntiSlam (Summer '00?, 'Secretary Day-Evening', 'Baby Al'), 2000 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0042)
      Original format: Hi8
    - "Allesandro's Robosapien tryout, Fringe '99", 1999 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0043)
    - "AntiSlam", January 2, 2004 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0044)
    - "AntiSlam", Octiber 24, 2001 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0045)
    - "AntiSlam (no audio)", March 24, 2004 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0046)
    - "AntiSlam", January 4, 2004 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0047)
    - "AntiSlam", May 26, 2004 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0048)
    - "AntiSlam", May 5, 2004 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0049)
    - "AntiSlam", June 16, 2004 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0050)
    - "AntiSlam", June 9,2004 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0005)
    - "AntiSlam", June 22, 2004 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0052)
    - "Chronis stuff, Tompkins Park", undated (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0053)
    - "EP!; Convention; Music Builders; 3/26/1999", March 26, 1999 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0054)
    - "Pixelface; Tesla party, 1999; 7/10/2004 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0055)
    - "Neal Medlyn; Mr. LES (no audio)", January 2004 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0056)
    - "CVR", undated (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0057)
    - "Disco Sucks (2 min.); Faceboy 500 (no audio)", February 1, 2004 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0058)
    - "Don't Ask Don't Tell trailer", undated (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0059)
      Currently available until duplication occurs.
    - "Don't Ask Don't Tell trailer", undated (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0060)
    - "Drama Desk Nomination", April 25, 2000 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0061)
    - "Face[boy]", June 6, 2004 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0062)
    - "Faceboy", May 16, 2004 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0063)
    - "Faceboy", July 4, 2004 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0064)
    - "Faceboy", May 23, 2004 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0065)
    - "Monster 2001, #2" (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0066)
    - "LG", undated (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0067)
    - "1) ???; 2)Magical Madness", July 27, 2001 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0068)
    - "Manifestations: War is Cold, Episode 2: Viva La Revolucion (both nights)", 1997 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0069)
    - "Manifestations: War is Cold, Episode 2: Viva la Revolucion (2 nights; video by Steve Zacks)", 1997 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0070)
    - "Manifestations: War is Cold, Episode 3: Factfinding tour (tight)" (side of cassette reads: "War is Cold #5"), January 10, 1998 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0071)
    - "Manifestations: War is Cold, Episode 3: Factfinding tour; + Flint", January 9, 1998 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0072)
    - "Manifestations: War is Cold, Episode 4: Operation Magna, (both nights)", January 30-31, 1998 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0073)
    - "Manifestations 5", 1998 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0074)
    - "Manifestations: War is Cold, Episode 5", 1998 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0075)
    - "Manifestations: War is Cold, Episode 5: The Trans-Siberian Express", 1998 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0076)
    - "Manifestations: War is Cold, Episode 6: Nutcracker", 1998 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0077)
    - "Manifestations: War is Cold, Episode 8: Subterranean Homesick Blues", 5/31/1998 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0078)
    - "Manifestations: War is Cold, Episode 8: Subterranean Homesick Blues", May 30, 1998 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0079)
    - "Manifestations: War is Cold, Episode 9", August 29-30, 1998 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0080)
    - "Match Game", April 2004 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0081)
    - "Mermaid Parade, Monster Parade", 2001 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0082)
    - "Mikon shots; Face (no audio)", February 29, 2004 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0083)
      Currently unavailble until duplication occurs.
    - "9/4/04", September 4, 2004 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0084)
    - "The Primary Principle, by Miroslaw Rajkowski (shot by Scott Kravet; Light & Sound by Steve Zacks)", July 11, 1998 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0085)
    - "Rev Jen", undated (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0086)
    - "Rev Jen's Halcyon Show; Autoevent #7", 1998 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0087)
    - "shoots for 360 (degrees)", undated (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0088)
    - "Tapp; Face", April 25, 2004 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0089)
    - "Tesla Coil video, by Nick Zedd", undated (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0090)
    - "Tesla moments; Faces", June 1, 2004; May 31, 2004 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0091)
    - "Two Wishes Kissing, + Kelly dancing...", undated (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0092)
    - "Two Wishes Kissing; War is Cold ep. 2 (last sc.); Steve (monologue)", undated (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0093)
      Currently unavialable until duplication occurs.
    - Untitled, undated (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0094)
      Original format: VHS-C
    - Untitled, undated (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0095)
    - Untitled, undated (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0096)
    - "Walker", September 30, 2000 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0097)
    - "Mr. LES Farewell Address", undated (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0152)
    - "Mr. LES show [crossed out]; movies" [Subseries C?], undated (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0153)
    - "Scott Kravet, Museum of Experience, Sex Workers (21 Min.)", undated (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0154)
  - Subseries C: Miscellaneous
    - "Queen of Outer Space", 1986 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0005)
    - "Invasion of the Blood Farmers", 1986 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0006)
    - "Mercury Rising", 1987 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0007)
    - "Rollerball", 1975 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0008)
    - "Leap of Faith", 1992 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0009)
    - "Planet of the Apes", 1998 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0010)
      Original Format: VHS
    - "Greatest Heroes of the Bible: The Ten Commandments/Abraham's Sacrifice", 1979 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0011)
    - "The Running Man", 1987 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0012)
    - "Lidsville, Vol. 1", undated (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0013)
    - "Millenium Fever" (Subseries B?), undated (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0014)
    - "WAHL Home Haircutting How-To Video", undated (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0015)
    - "Bubblegum Crisis #5", undated (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0017)
    - "Everting The Sphere" (Subseries B?), undated (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0018)
    - Untitled, undated (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0020)
    - Untitled, undated (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0021)
    - Untitled, undated (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0022)
    - "Bubblegum Crisis I,II,III,IV", undated (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0024)
    - "(e)" (Subseries B?), undated (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0025)
    - "Raw Justice", undated (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0026)
    - "Stretch Marks vid" (Subseries B?), undated (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0027)
    - "Blazing Saddles", undated (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0028)
    - "Belle de Jour", undated (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0029)
    - "Fists of Fury", undated (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0030)
    - "Odyssey Animation, R.O. Ernst", August 1997 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0031)
    - "J. Bond 147", undated (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0032)
    - "BJ, Scott Hess at HERE", undated (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0033)
      Format: VHS
    - Untitled, undated (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0034)
    - Untitled, undated (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0035)
    - "The First Day of the Beginning of the End of the World, Jenny Stark", 1999 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0037)
    - "A Fool and His Money", undated (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0038)
    - "a52, MVBMS, JP Morgan..." (container reads: "To Record"), undated (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0098)
    - "Aguirre Der Zorn Gottes (The Wrath of God, with Klaus Kinski)", undated (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0099)
    - "Al Fresco; (c) R. Shirley, Q. Williams", 1998 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0100)
    - "60 Minutes of all Cornelius vids & Live Destruction; Directed by Corneius, Harvard Design, Help! Films", 2000 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0101)
    - "Anarchy USA; The Commies are Coming; Red Menace; The Code of Conduct", 1965; 1953; undated; undated (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0102)
    - "Architecture of Doom (about Nazi culture)", undated (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0103)
    - "Attack of the 50ft. Woman", 1958 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0104)
    - "Babe", 1995 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0105)
    - "Battle of Algiers", 1993 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0106)
    - "Big Trouble in Little China; Twins; Moon Over Parador", undated (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0107)
    - "Black Magic M66 (48 min); Appleseed (70 min, Japanese cyberpunk animation)", undated (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0108)
    - "Bondage, Vol. 1", undated (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0109)
    - "The Bride of Frankenstein", 1991 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0110)
    - "Broadway...A History of the Musical: Vol II, Broadway Comes of Age", undated (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0111)
    - "Brooklyn Burlesque Blitz; 1/12, Hour 3, Hosted by Naughtia Nice & Bastard Keith", undated (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0112)
      Original format: DVD
    - "Cereal Commercials Vol. 1 & 2", undated (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0113)
    - "Cheesedick, a tape by Matthew L. Weiss (Langdon-Boom Productions)", 2001 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0114)
    - "16mm Classroom Films (Nostalgia Video)", undated (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0115)
    - "Creepy Clips from Classic Horror Films!", 1995 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0116)
    - "The Prisoner (Disc 2)" (container reads: "Demon Womb Check Disk"), July 21, 1999 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0117)
    - "Diary of a Chambermaid (revised)", May 10. 2001 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0118)
    - "Diderot and the Last Luminare (Erika Suderburg)", 1992 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0119)
    - "Los Diez Mandamientos (The Ten Commandments)", 1980 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0120)
    - "Comedy Central: 10PM -Dr Katz, ep. 601; 10:30PM -Mark Curry", June 15 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0121)
    - "Fishing with John", March 17, 1999 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0122)
    - "Flash Gordon (Vol. 1)", 1998 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0123)
    - "Flash Gordon (Vol. 2)", 1998 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0124)
    - "Flying in Airplane (Florida to NY), Steve Zacks" [Subseries B?], undated (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0125)
    - "Frankie & Johnny", 1992 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0126)
    - "Augustin Gimel - 1305, Radar, DIN 16538/39, Il n'y a rien de plus inutile qu'un organe, 90", undated (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0127)
      Original format: VHS [PAL]
    - "Godzilla 2000", 1999 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0128)
    - "Good News New York", undated (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0129)
    - "TCM's Brownlow & Gill Comedy Masters Series - Harold Lloyd: The Third Genius", April 18, 1997 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0130)
    - "Hitler's homemovies; Three Songs about Lenin ('39)", undated (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0131)
    - "Hitler [illegible annotations] Quex", undated (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0132)
    - "Hornet Magic (The Boeing Company)", 2000 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0133)
    - "How To Get Ahead In Advertising, 6/7/01", June 7, 2001 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0134)
    - "In Our Garden", undated (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0135)
    - "Invasion of the Bee Girls", undated (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0136)
    - "Invasion of the Saucer Men", 1993 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0137)
    - "Ivan the Terrible, pt. 2", February 20, 2001 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0138)
    - "Jericho Fever", 1993 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0139)
    - "The Jungle Book", undated (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0140)
    - "Justin Charisma", undated (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0141)
    - "Lamb, Fear of Fours video reel", 1999 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0142)
    - "Life in Bud, Nick Lindsay", undated (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0143)
    - "Life on Earth", October 10, 2000 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0144)
    - "Fourth Annual Media That Matters Film Festival", 2004 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0145)
    - "The Troika Organization, 'Meet Me In St. Louis', television spot & selected songs", undated (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0146)
    - "The Miracle of the One Visit Denture", undated (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0147)
    - "Miracle on 34th Street", 1993 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0148)
    - "Monster From Green Hell", 1990 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0149)
    - "Monster From A Prehistoric Planet", 1989 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0150)
    - "MPFC German Episode 2", September 5, 2000 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0151)
    - "9 to 5", 1995 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0155)
    - "None of the Above (trailer), Insular Pictures, Frank Barrera", undated (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0156)
    - Misc. taped programs on Nazism, undated (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0157)
    - "Oui We, by Anthony Howard", undated (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0158)
    - "Integrated Orbital Implants, Inc. Patient Education Video", undated (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0159)
    - "USA Network: People's Court episodes 2182/2183", undated (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0160)
    - "Piano Man and Medea excerpts, Dor Green", undated (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0161)
    - "Pierrot le Fou", September 25, 1998 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0162)
    - "Porky's II: The Next Day", 1983 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0163)
    - "Prehistoric Women", 1985 (Box 14, Media ID: 2253.0164)
    - "The Prisoner Vol. 7", March 5, 2001 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0165)
    - "Reveille, dir. Bruce Bennett (C:U storefront cameo)", 2001 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0166)
    - "Rock 'n' Roll Frankenstein music video", undated (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0167)
    - "Rock n Roll Frankenstein trailer", undated (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0168)
    - "Rock 'N' Roll Frankenstein trailer", undated (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0169)
    - "Safari, a film by Paul Sullivan", undated (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0170)
    - "Salo check disc", undated (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0171)
    - "Saya for Kristina Daniels", undated (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0172)
    - "Dan Cronin as Sergi, video by Paul Sullivan", undated (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0173)
    - "Shrimpdiabloinmypants Film Festival", July 10, 1999 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0174)
    - "Erika Suderburg, Somatography", 2000 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0175)
    - "South Dakota Trilogy In Three Minutes", undated (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0176)
    - "The Adventures of Spunky and Tadpole", 1985 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0177)
    - "Sugar Hill", undated (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0178)
    - "Them!", undated (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0179)
    - "Thunderbirds Vol 3", January 8, 2001 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0180)
    - "To Have and Have Not", 1945 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0181)
    - "Topaz", undated (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0182)
    - "Toys in Playland", 1997 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0183)
    - "Traces: Three Takes on the Generational Separation of Family", undated (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0184)
    - "Twilight of the Dark Master", undated (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0185)
    - "UFOs Are Real, a Brandon Chase film", 1993 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0186)
    - Untitled, undated (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0187)
    - Untitled, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0188)
    - "LG" (?; crossed out text: "up tree with chainsaw"), 1997 (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0189)
    - Untitled (flower stamp), undated (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0190)
    - Untitled, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0191)
    - Untitled, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0192)
    - Untitled, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0193)
    - Untitled, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0194)
    - Untitled, (starred), undated (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0195)
    - untitled, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0196)
      Currently unavailable until duplications occurs.
    - Untitled, container has crossed out text: "Opera and Ghost of Canterbury", undated (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0197)
    - "The Violent Years (Mamie Van Doren hosts Teenage Theater)", 1985 (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0198)
    - "White Disabled Talent (excerpts)", undated (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0199)
    - "Julian Whatley, Director of Photography, Commercial/MV Reel, Series IX; Wildchild Editorial", undated (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0200)
    - "CVR - ABC News; Wolf's tape", March 22, 2000; undated (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0201)
    - "Vervolg: Eternal Jew (Wolf NYC)", undated (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0202)
    - "Nazi UFOs & Illuminati Conspiracy; The Eternal Jew; nazi propaganda (Wolf NYC #1)", undated (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0203)
    - "Love Poem Cinema" (Korean video), 2000 (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0204)
    - Korean video, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0205)
    - Foreign Language Video, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0206)
- Series VI: Audio
  Series VI: Audio consists of original and miscellaneous audio recordings of Collective: Unconscious and other groups. Subseries B, Originals, contains recordings of Collective: Unconscious productions, most documenting anti-slams and Faceboy. Subseries C, Miscellaneous, includes commercial albums, mixed tapes, and unidentified materials.
  - Subseries A: Access Copies
    Access copies for audio originals may not yet be available. Please contact a Fales Archivist.
  - Subseries B: Originals
    - "AntiSlam", February 10, 2004 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0207)
      Original format: audiocassette
    - "AntiSlam", December 2, 2004 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0208)
    - "AntiSlam pt 1", February 24, 2004 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0209)
    - "AntiSlam pt 2", February 24, 2004 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0210)
    - "AntiSlam", March 4, 2004 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0211)
      Currently unavaiable until duplication occurs.